<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WETHOD / Learning Center</title>
    <link>https://support.wethod.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WETHOD / Learning Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://support.wethod.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Profit &amp; Loss</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/group-profit-loss/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/group-profit-loss/index/</guid>
      <description> Overview An aggregated view for the profit &amp;amp; loss report
Note
Data in this section use a daily cache to keep things fast. If you need something more updated please use the &amp;ldquo;Refresh data&amp;rdquo; button.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</guid>
      <description>Warm Up Visit app.wethod.com/registration to create your team and get a 14 days free trial, we don&amp;rsquo;t force you to insert a credit card and you can take advantage of our tutorial.
Setup Your Company By clicking on your initials (in the top right corner), the Settings menu will be shown and you can select the Company section to configure your team.
Now you can invite your team members by visiting the Team section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desk</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/desk/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/desk/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Desk is your private space and your favorite place. Here you can find a set of utilities and widgets all for you.
 Activities This box collects all the items that were assigned to you in any boards. You can scroll through them, search by item name and mark them as completed without going to the dedicated page. If this box is empty try to add a column &amp;ldquo;Member&amp;rdquo; in a board and set yourself as &amp;ldquo;Activity&amp;rsquo;s assignee&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenues</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/group-revenues/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/group-revenues/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview An aggregated view for the revenues report
Revenues by month Here you have the yearly revenues of your group, distributed on a monthly basis. As you can see in the legend, there are various notable things in the chart:
 Production based on companies&amp;rsquo; project status Production plan based on companies&amp;rsquo; production plan Bluesky based on companies&amp;rsquo; bluesky Monthly production value obtained by dividing the target (which you can edit from the company&amp;rsquo;s profit &amp;amp; loss and displayed inside the clock chart on the right) for 12 (the number of months per year) Production trend based on the production of the last three years   Revenues by client A table where you can appreciate how much production has been generated from each company of the group an towards each of their clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/group-setup/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/group-setup/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview If you need to manage various company belonging to the same holding, this is the right tool for you: enabling the group module lets you appreciate aggregates statistics about all of your companies and made possibile to track intercompany work.
Hierarchy Once you have enabled the group module, you can start building the hierarchy of your group: drag companies inside the graph, create levels and name them.
 Clients normalizer From here you can map company-level clients onto group-wide clusters, this is useful for those reports which displays values related to clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alerts</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/alerts/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/alerts/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview An alert is an inconsistency regarding the user. Each alert has a priority (indicated by its color):
 Red alerts have an high priority and must be solved as soon as possible; Yellow alerts have a low priority and can be seen more as advices; Blue alerts are reminders of minor fixes.  Positioning the cursor over an alert will display a description of the problem.
Some alerts depends on parameters that you can customize using the Alerts Engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 19:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The pipeline is the core of Wethod. Here is where you can find and manage all the opportunities and projects of your company.
The different steps and phases of a project can be managed in different sections:
 Basket Pipeline Opportunities Projects  Basket The Basket contains all the opportunities that are not well-defined yet. You can see it as a place where to put all the ideas that you usually write on a notebook or on a Post-It.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budget</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 11:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The budget is where you can list all the resources you think you&amp;rsquo;ll need for the project.
 Basically, this is the place where you define (for a project):
 How many people you need; Which experience levels you need; Which tasks are needed to get the job done; Who will do what; The external costs; The selling price.  Done? Now the budget must be approved by a supervisor and, once approved, the project manager can start planning and creating orders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 19:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The planning has two section:
 People Allocation helps you to look for teammates availability, resources allocation and check if the budget quota is respected. Projects&amp;rsquo; Heatmap shows the daily amount of people planned on each project. It also offers a milestone system that allows your team to have an overview on the scheduled events. Production Plan where you can express the percentage of the project&amp;rsquo;s total value you are going to produce in each month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 13:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview WETHOD follows a weekly cycle: we think that a week is a good trade-off between the need to control the project&amp;rsquo;s progress as much as possible and the need to not burden the control activities.
Every Friday an e-mail will remind:
 Each project manager to compile the Project Status for its projects;
 Each collaborator to compile the Timesheet for the projects he worked on.
  Timesheet Remember to insert only the real worked hours, cheating isn&amp;rsquo;t useful to anybody.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 10:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview All the data you insert in WETHOD are used to generate, weekly and automatically, a set of reports useful to monitor the projects&amp;rsquo; progress.
Project Report Each Monday, utilising data provided by Timesheet, Project Status and Budget, a Project Report is automatically created.
Budget Consumption / Project Status This section shows the budget consumption of the project, compared to its progress:
 If the project is above the diagonal: it&amp;rsquo;s using a lot of days but it&amp;rsquo;s progressing slowly than predictions based on budget; If the project is under the diagonal: it&amp;rsquo;s using few days but it&amp;rsquo;s progressing faster than predictions based on budget; If the project is on the diagonal: it&amp;rsquo;s planned and managed correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 18:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Dashboard is basically a set of widgets, any one of which can be added or removed and customized by the user.
 Widgets Adding a new widget to your dashboard is very easy: just click on the “+” sign and pick one from the list of the available widgets.
 Alerts This widget shows all the inconsistencies regarding the user. Each alert has a priority (indicated by its color):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 10:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</guid>
      <description>Orders In this section you can see all your orders and create new ones.
 Create a new order  Click button New Order and a sidebar will open.    Insert project name. The job order will be automatically filled by the system. Compile all the required fields Click on the &amp;ldquo;save&amp;rdquo; button Your order will be added to the list  Order&amp;rsquo;s fields description  Project: the target Project Job Order: automatically filled selecting the project Supplier: the target Supplier for this Order Purchase Code: an identifier for the Order Value: the total cost of this Order Area: the area of the budget this Order is about Date: the issue date of this Order Duration: answers to the question &amp;ldquo;when this order will used for the project?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 10:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</guid>
      <description>Account Here you set your name, surname and password.
If you have the right permissions, you can:
 Change your invoice details; Import existing projects.  Team Since you have the right permissions, you can: invite people, assign specific roles and allow special permissions.
To invite a new teammate:
 Click on the top left &amp;ldquo;+ new user&amp;rdquo; button; Assign a user level, a *role *and the email address of the person you want to invite; Click the &amp;ldquo;invite&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profit &amp; Loss</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/profit-loss/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/profit-loss/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview This page provides an overview of the budgetary slippages between a company&amp;rsquo;s projected revenues and its expenses, as well as its budget target over a given period of time. The three columns budget, forecast 1 and forecast 2 can be used to set the company&amp;rsquo;s financial goals for each quarter of the year.
The column budget in the revenues row is used to set the revenues&amp;rsquo; target for the company, which is used in the widget Revenue Clock and in the report Production Value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenues</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/revenues/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/revenues/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here you can see the value of your projects for each month of the current year.
The monthly distribution is achieved by looking at the production plan of every project, for example: if a project is evaluated 10 K with 3 K planned to be produced in January and 7 K planned to be produced in February, the value of this project will contribute with 3 K to the January&amp;rsquo;s revenues and with 7 K to February&amp;rsquo;s revenues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External Costs</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/external-costs/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/external-costs/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview In this section you can see the yearly distribution for all your projects&amp;rsquo; external costs. The amount ordered by projects is dispalyed month by month based on the period they cover, in particular:
 Orders&amp;rsquo; value follows the orders&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Period of Supply&amp;rdquo;, for example: an order of 3.000 with a period from January to June will weigh 500 on each month from January to June Travels&amp;rsquo; value follows the departure and return date of each Travel (if the travel is a one-way trip then all costs will weigh on the departure date).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gross Margin</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/gross-margin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/gross-margin/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here you can see the details about Profit &amp;amp; Loss&amp;rsquo; gross margin for each month of the current year.
A project&amp;rsquo;s gross margin is the difference between its revenues and its external costs.
Three important indicators are given in the first rows:
 Total: the sum of all your projects&amp;rsquo; gross margin, per month
 Bluesky: the dfference between revenues&amp;rsquo; bluesky and external costs&amp;rsquo; bluesky
 Delta revenues target: the dfference between revenues&amp;rsquo; delta revenues target and external costs&amp;rsquo; delta revenues target</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payroll</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/payroll/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/payroll/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here you can manage your employees&amp;rsquo; salary and all the other related costs.
Totals First thing that you see is a table which shows, by month and for the selected year, the company&amp;rsquo;s headcount and the sum of costs related to payroll.
The sum of costs are displayed in the Total row, they&amp;rsquo;re a combination of costs coming from placeholders, employees and adjustments.
The Headcount shows the amount of employees and placeholders with costs that impact on the company for the selected year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G &amp; A</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/general-admin/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/general-admin/index/</guid>
      <description> Overview Here you can list all your general and administratrion costs. This is the right place to put all that costs which aren&amp;rsquo;t about external costs, payroll or marketing.
Each cost has:
 Start month
 End month
 Net month
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/marketing/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/marketing/index/</guid>
      <description> Overview This is the right place to put all that costs related to the promotion of your products or services.
Each cost has:
 Start month
 End month
 Net month
  Use the Import costs button to copy all the marketing costs&amp;rsquo; rows from the previous year.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capex</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/capex/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/capex/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview This section provides an overview of all investment project values meant as Capital Expenditures.
 Total CapEx costs for each project are divided into:
 Payroll costs: all the costs derived from employees’ levels’ rates External costs  You can edit the CapEx percentage field to tell Wethod the amount of investment to consider from the project.
To mark all costs in a project as CapEx, just assign that project a job order category where &amp;ldquo;CapEx&amp;rdquo; is flagged</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoice Plan</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/invoice-plan/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 08:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/invoice-plan/index/</guid>
      <description> Overview From here you can see the invoice plans of all your company&amp;rsquo;s projects.
This is basically a summary of the view you have from pipeline, where you can access each project&amp;rsquo;s invoice plan one by one.
Each row in this view represents a project and carries with it a bunch of information:
 Whether the plan is automatically or manually distributed Name and client for the project The monthly plan&amp;rsquo;s distribution for the current year: for each month you can appreciate the plan&amp;rsquo;s value and the actual invoices amount (colored with lower opacity) The total plan&amp;rsquo;s amount for the current year   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Order Plan</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/order-plan/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 08:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/order-plan/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview From here you can see the orders&amp;rsquo; amount grouped by projects.
The way you will visualise your orders depends on the preference you have specified in the Company Settings page.
Each row in this view represents a project and carries with it the following information:
 Name, PM and client for the project The order&amp;rsquo;s costs for the current year For each month you can see the planned orders&amp;rsquo; amount and the approved orders amount (coloured in grey or in red if lower than planned) The total planned amount for the current year   Note</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 17:08:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</guid>
      <description>(function(q,u,e,s,t,i,o,n) { o=u.getElementsByTagName(e)[0]; n=u.createElement(s),n.async=1,n.defer=1,n.src=i; o.appendChild(n) })(window,document,&#34;head&#34;,&#34;script&#34;,&#34;res_pars&#34;, &#34;https://goresponsa.com/widgets/57a0713be0e2ee8a8c001270.js&#34;);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</guid>
      <description>Absolute Project Progress This value indicates how much a project is advanced since its beginning. For example, a project with:
 Budget days: 200; Last project status: 40;  Has an absolute project progress of: ( 200 - 40 ) / 200 * 100 = 80 % .
Bluesky It represents the value you think is missing in order to reach an hypothetical overall value.
For example: if I have an actual value of 5 but I know that, in a particular moment in time, actual value will reach the final value of 7, then I can use a Bluesky of 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover WETHOD</title>
      <link>https://support.wethod.com/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.wethod.com/index/</guid>
      <description>What It Is WETHOD is the online tool to manage people and projects in a collaborative way. We aim to make the project management simple, distributing the responsibilities among all the team members and reducing stress derived from projects organization.
The result is a deeply integrated system that manages all the information which are essential for a project-oriented company: budget, planning, timesheet and activity report.
This enables WETHOD to create a system where everybody collaborate and keep information up to date, a system that rewards who done well and warns the others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>