<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WETHOD / Learning Center</title>
    <link>http://support.wethod.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WETHOD / Learning Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://support.wethod.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</guid>
      <description>Warm Up Visit app.wethod.com/registration to create your team and get a 14 days free trial, we don&amp;rsquo;t force you to insert a credit card and you can take advantage of our tutorial.
Setup Your Company By clicking on your initials (in the top right corner), the Settings menu will be shown and you can select the Company section to configure your team.
Now you can invite your team members by visiting the Team section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 19:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Dashboard is basically a set of widgets, any one of which can be added or removed and customized by the user.
 Widgets Adding a new widget to your dashboard is very easy: just click on the “+” sign and pick one from the list of the available widgets.
 Alerts This widget shows all the inconsistencies regarding the user. Each alert has a priority (indicated by its color):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alerts</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/alerts/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 18:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/alerts/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview An alert is an inconsistency regarding the user. Each alert has a priority (indicated by its color):
 Red alerts have an high priority and must be solved as soon as possible; Yellow alerts have a low priority and can be seen more as advices.  Positioning the cursor over an alert will display a description of the problem.
Some alerts depends on parameters that you can customize using the Alerts Engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Everything starts from Pipeline, here is where opportunities and projects are listed, both of them are defined by a small amount of significant information:
 Name: how are you going to call it?; Client: for who are you going to work?; Value (in K): what&amp;rsquo;s the estimated price to the client?; Percentage of external costs; Category: which type of project is it?; Probability: how likely this project is going to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budget</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 13:04:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The budget is where you can list all the resources you think you&amp;rsquo;ll need for the project.
 Basically, this is the place where you try define (for a project):
 How many people you need;
 Which experience levels you need;
 Which tasks are needed to get the job done;
 Who will do what;
 The external costs;
 The selling price.
  Done? Now the budget must be approved by a supervisor and, once approved, the project manager can start planning and creating orders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The planning has two section: People Allocation and Projects&amp;rsquo; Heatmap, the first one is useful to look at teammates availability, allocate them for projects and check that you respect the budget quota; the second section shows the daily amount of people needed by each project, it also offers a milestone system that allows your team to have an overview on the scheduled events.
Everything is arranged into a six weeks calendar, you can explore past and future using the horizontal scroll or clicking on the top right arrow navigator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 15:51:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview WETHOD follows a weekly cycle: we think that a week is a good trade-off between the need to control the project&amp;rsquo;s progress as much as possible and the need to not burden the control activities.
Every Friday an e-mail will remind:
 Each project manager to compile the Project Status for its projects;
 Each collaborator to compile the Timesheet for the projects he worked on.
  Timesheet At the end of each week, type in here the actual hours you&amp;rsquo;ve spent working on the projects you are involved in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:01:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview All the data you insert in WETHOD are used to generate, weekly and automatically, a set of reports useful to monitoring the projects&amp;rsquo; progress.
Project Report Each Monday, utilising data provided by Timesheet, Project Status and Budget, a Project Report is automatically created.
Budget Consumption / Project Status This section shows the budget consumption of the project, compared to its progress:
 If the project is above the diagonal: it&amp;rsquo;s using a lot of days but it&amp;rsquo;s progressing slowly than predictions based on budget; If the project is under the diagonal: it&amp;rsquo;s using few days but it&amp;rsquo;s progressing faster than predictions based on budget; If the project is on the diagonal: it&amp;rsquo;s planned and managed correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:06:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</guid>
      <description>Orders In this section you can see all your orders and create new ones.
To create an order:
 Click on the top left &amp;ldquo;+ order&amp;rdquo; button and an empty order will be added to the list Compile the required fields Click on the &amp;ldquo;create&amp;rdquo; button  After creating an order you can send it and approve it. Once you click on the &amp;ldquo;send&amp;rdquo; button, an e-mail will be sent to the address provided in the settings&amp;rsquo; Email Bot section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:09:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</guid>
      <description>Tutorial From here you can access a quick and clear tutorial that will teach you all the secrets behind WETHOD, but remember: with great power comes great responsibility.
Clicking on &amp;ldquo;let me try&amp;rdquo; will pause the tutorial and let you take a look around, to resume the tutorial just click on the bottom right button.
Clicking on &amp;ldquo;skip tour&amp;rdquo; will close the tutorial.
Account Here you set your name, surname and password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profit &amp; Loss</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/profit-loss/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/profit-loss/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here you can see how much your company has earned or has lost during each month of the current year, the &amp;ldquo;Profit &amp;amp; Loss&amp;rdquo; row shows you this piece of information.
This data is obtained by subtracting from the revenues of all the costs faced by the company. The costs can be of various kinds:
 External costs
 Payroll
 G &amp;amp; A
 Marketing
  We provide you with two subtotal in order to better understand the final value of profit &amp;amp; loss for the company:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenues</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/revenues/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/revenues/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here you can see the value of your projects for each month of the current year.
The monthly distribution is achieved by looking at the production plan of every project, for example: if a project is evaluated 10 K with 3 K planned to be produced in January and 7 K planned to be produced in February, the value of this project will contribute with 3 K to the January&amp;rsquo;s revenues and with 7 K to February&amp;rsquo;s revenues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External Costs</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/external-costs/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/external-costs/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here you can see the external costs listed in your projects&amp;rsquo; budget for each month of the current year.
The monthly distribution is achieved by looking at the production plan of every project, for example: if a project has a value of 10 K with 3 K planned to be produced in January and 7 K planned to be produced in February, we can also say that you planned to invoice 30% in January and 70% in February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payroll</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/payroll/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:41:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/payroll/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of all your employees&amp;rsquo; salary for the current year.
Each Employee has at least a segment which represents a work contract between that employee and the company. Every segment has:
 Start month
 End month
 Gross monthly salary
 Taxes
  You can access the segments for a specific employee just by clicking on the employee&amp;rsquo;s row. Each time you edit a list of the segments, this influences the employee&amp;rsquo;s salary distribution: a line where all segments are visually represented, allowing you to quickly understand how many times the salary of an employee is changed during the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G &amp; A</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/general-admin/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/general-admin/index/</guid>
      <description> Overview Here you can list all your general and administratrion costs. This is the right place to put all that costs which aren&amp;rsquo;t about external costs, payroll or marketing.
Each cost has:
 Start month
 End month
 Net month
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/marketing/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/marketing/index/</guid>
      <description> Overview This is the right place to put all that costs related to the promotion of your products or services.
Each cost has:
 Start month
 End month
 Net month
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 17:08:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</guid>
      <description>(function(q,u,e,s,t,i,o,n) { o=u.getElementsByTagName(e)[0]; n=u.createElement(s),n.async=1,n.defer=1,n.src=i; o.appendChild(n) })(window,document,&#34;head&#34;,&#34;script&#34;,&#34;res_pars&#34;, &#34;https://goresponsa.com/widgets/57a0713be0e2ee8a8c001270.js&#34;);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 17:31:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</guid>
      <description>Absolute Project Progress This value indicates how much a project is advanced since its beginning. For example, a project with:
 Budget days: 200;
 Last project status: 40;
  Has an absolute project progress of: ( 200 - 40 ) / 200 * 100 = 80 % .
Bluesky It represents the value you think is missing in order to reach an hypothetical overall value.
For example: if I have an actual value of 5 but I know that, in a particular moment in time, actual value will reach the final value of 7, then I can use a Bluesky of 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover WETHOD</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/index/</guid>
      <description>What It Is WETHOD is the online tool to manage people and projects in a collaborative way. We aim to make the project management simple, distributing the responsibilities among all the team members and reducing stress derived from projects organization.
The result is a deeply integrated system that manages all the information which are essential for a project-oriented company: budget, planning, timesheet and activity report.
This enables WETHOD to create a system where everybody collaborate and keep information up to date, a system that rewards who done well and warns the others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>