<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WETHOD / Learning Center</title>
    <link>http://support.wethod.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WETHOD / Learning Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://support.wethod.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</guid>
      <description>Warm Up Visit app.wethod.com/registration to create your team and get a 14 days free trial, we don&amp;rsquo;t force you to insert a credit card and you can take advantage of our tutorial.
Setup Your Company By clicking on your initials (in the top right corner), the Settings menu will be shown and you can select the Company section to configure your team.
Now you can invite your team members by visiting the Team section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 19:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Dashboard is basically a set of widgets any one of which can be added, removed and customized by the user.
 Widgets Add a new widget to your dashboard is so easy: just click on the &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; and pick one from the list of the available widgets.
 Alerts This widget shows all the inconsistencies regarding the user. Each alert has a priority (indicated by its color):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alerts</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/alerts/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 18:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/alerts/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview This widget shows all the inconsistencies regarding the user. Each alert has a priority (indicated by its color):
 Red alerts have an high priority and must be solved as soon as possible;
 Yellow alerts have a low priority and can be seen more as advices.
  Hovering the cursor over an alert will display a description of the problem.
Yellow Alerts Unsent Order This alert is shown to the project manager who have created orders not sent yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Everything starts from Pipeline, here is where opportunities and projects are listed, both of them are defined by a small amount of significant information:
 Name: how are you going to call it?;
 Client: for who are you going to work?;
 Value (in K): what&amp;rsquo;s the estimated price to the client?;
 Percentage of external costs;
 Category: which type of project is it?;
 Probability: how likely this project is going to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budget</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 13:04:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The budget is where you can list all the resources you think you&amp;rsquo;ll need for the project.
 Basically, this is the place where you try define (for a project):
 How many people you need;
 Which experience levels you need;
 Which tasks are needed to get the job done;
 Who will do what;
 The external costs;
 The selling price.
  Done? Now the budget must be approved by a supervisor and, once approved, the project manager can start planning and creating orders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The planning is useful to look at teammates availability, allocate them for projects and check that you respect the budget quota.
You can plan a person by half-days: we think it&amp;rsquo;s not worth planning by more fine-grained amounts of time. If your tasks require less time, just group them!
Note
You cannot plan people for the current day: if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what you have to do when you arrive at the office, how can you be productive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 15:51:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview WETHOD follows a weekly cycle: we think that a week is a good trade-off between the need to control the project&amp;rsquo;s progress as much as possible and the need to not burden the control activities.
Every Friday an e-mail will remind:
 Each project manager to compile the Project Status for its projects;
 Each collaborator to compile the Timesheet for the projects he worked on.
  Timesheet At the end of each week, type in here the actual hours you&amp;rsquo;ve spent working on the projects you are involved in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:01:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview All the data you insert in WETHOD are used to generate, weekly and automatically, a set of reports useful to monitoring the projects&amp;rsquo; progress.
Project Report Each Monday, utilising data provided by Timesheet, Project Status and Budget, a Project Report is automatically created.
Budget Consumption / Project Status This section shows the budget consumption of the project, compared to its progress:
 If the project is above the diagonal: it&amp;rsquo;s using a lot of days but it&amp;rsquo;s progressing slowly than predictions based on budget;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:06:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</guid>
      <description>Orders In this section you can view all your orders and create new ones. Once you click on the &amp;ldquo;Send&amp;rdquo; button, an e-mail is sent to the address provided in the Email Bot section.
To create a order:
 Click on the top left &amp;ldquo;+ order&amp;rdquo; button and an empty order will be added to the list;
 Compile the order&amp;rsquo;s empty fields;
 Click on the &amp;ldquo;create&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:09:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</guid>
      <description>Tutorial From here you can access a quick and clear tutorial that will teach you all the secrets behind WETHOD, but remember: with great power comes great responsibility.
Clicking on &amp;ldquo;let me try&amp;rdquo; will pause the tutorial and let you take a look around, to resume the tutorial just click on the bottom right button.
Clicking on &amp;ldquo;skip tour&amp;rdquo; will close the tutorial.
Account Here you set your name, surname and password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profit &amp; Loss</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/profit-loss/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/profit-loss/index/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenues</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/revenues/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/revenues/index/</guid>
      <description>Revenue is the amount of money that a company actually receives during a specific year, it is calculated by multiplying the price at which goods or services are sold by the number of units or amount sold.
In this section the projects of the Pipeline considering their probability and duration are listed showing the value they have per month.
The Value which is the sum of the present values of all the projects per month and year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External Costs</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/external-costs/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/external-costs/index/</guid>
      <description>The External Costs are all the indirect costs that you have to consider in your business.
In this section all the external costs of all the projects are listed per month and year.
Notice that here Bluesky is not shown month per month but is represented by an unic percentage on the Revenues’ Bluesky.
The External Costs table can only be visualized and not directly modified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G &amp; A</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/general-admin/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/general-admin/index/</guid>
      <description>In this section are listed all the administration’s costs of the projects per month.
With administration costs we mean all the costs that your business can have that are related to the management and administration overall.
In order to add a G&amp;amp;A cost you just have to select the starting and ending date, choosing the value that you will pay monthly and save, in this way you will see the total cost for the indicated period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/marketing/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:24:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/marketing/index/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 17:08:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</guid>
      <description>(function(q,u,e,s,t,i,o,n) { o=u.getElementsByTagName(e)[0]; n=u.createElement(s),n.async=1,n.defer=1,n.src=i; o.appendChild(n) })(window,document,&#34;head&#34;,&#34;script&#34;,&#34;res_pars&#34;, &#34;https://goresponsa.com/widgets/57a0713be0e2ee8a8c001270.js&#34;);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 17:31:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</guid>
      <description>Absolute Project Progress This value indicates how much a project is advanced since its beginning. For example, a project with:
 Budget days: 200;
 Last project status: 40;
  Has an absolute project progress of: ( 200 - 40 ) / 200 * 100 = 80 % .
Budget Consumption This value indicates, for a project, the percentage of the budget days already used. This is calculated by comparing timesheet hours and budget days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover WETHOD</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/index/</guid>
      <description>What It Is WETHOD is the online tool to manage people and projects in a collaborative way. We aim to make the project management simple, distributing the responsibilities among all the team members and reducing stress derived from projects organization.
The result is a deeply integrated system that manages all the information which are essential for a project-oriented company: budget, planning, timesheet and activity report.
This enables WETHOD to create a system where everybody collaborate and keep information up to date, a system that rewards who done well and warns the others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>