<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WETHOD / Learning Center</title>
    <link>http://support.wethod.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WETHOD / Learning Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://support.wethod.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/getting-started/index/</guid>
      <description>Warm Up Visit app.wethod.com/registration to create your team and get a 14 days free trial, we don&amp;rsquo;t force you to insert a credit card and you can take advantage of our tutorial.
Setup Your Company By clicking on your initials (in the top right corner), the Settings menu will be shown and you can select the Company section to configure your team.
Now you can invite your team members by visiting the Team section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 19:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/dashboard/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Dashboard is basically a set of widget any one of which can be added, removed and customized by the user.
Widgets Add a new widget to your dashboard is so easy: just click on the &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; and pick one from the list of the available widgets.
 Alerts This widget shows all the inconsistencies regarding the user. Each alert has a priority (indicated by its color):
 Red alerts have an high priority and must be solved as soon as possible;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/pipeline/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Everything starts from Pipeline, here is where opportunities and projects are listed, both of them are defined by a small amount of significant information:
 Name;
 Client;
 Value (in €k);
 Percentage of external costs;
 Category;
 Probability.
  Pipeline has three subsections: Basket, Projects and Programs.
Basket The Basket contains all the project’s opportunity that are not well-defined yet. You can see it as a place where to put all the ideas that you usually write on a notebook or on a Post-It.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budget</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 13:04:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/budget/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview When the project has enough probability to start you can add a budget: the total resources available for the project, as internal and external costs. Choose the project in the projects pipeline by clicking on it and use the &amp;lsquo;Budget&amp;rsquo; button to enter the budget creation mode. Here you can define the budget structure: choose the default areas or create a budget from a previously saved template (see budget creation for more info).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/planning/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview
Look at teammates availability. Allocate half days, full days, or even weeks, checking that you respect the Budget quota.
That&amp;rsquo;s it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 15:51:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/friday/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Timesheet At the end of each week, type in the actual hours you&amp;rsquo;ve spent working on the Projects you are involved in under Friday menu.
The Timesheet section records data which will be used to determine the actual Budget consumption in terms of work hours for each Project. It&amp;rsquo;s all really easy, fast and simple.
Timesheets will never be the same again.
Project Status Once the weekend is near, each PM estimates the days left to finish the project and inserts this number in the Project Status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:01:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/reports/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Project Report Each Monday, utilising data provided by Project Status, Timesheet and Budget, a Project Report is automatically created.
Budget Consumption The Budget Consumption Report is an overview of all Projects in terms of resources and time spent on the project, allowing you to analyse their health at a glance.
Using filters, you can select the Projects you want to see and explore details such as billed hours, invoiced totals, and internal and external purchase orders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:06:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/finance/index/</guid>
      <description>Overview Orders In this section you can view all your orders and create new ones. Once you click on the &amp;ldquo;Send&amp;rdquo; button, an e-mail is sent to the address inserted in the Email Bot section.
You can create orders only for projects you have already provided with job order and budget.
Order&amp;rsquo;s value must be lower or equal then the external costs entered in the budget.
Invoices In this section you can view all your invoices and create new ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 12:09:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/settings/index/</guid>
      <description>Tutorial Account Puoi cambiare nome, cognome, password.
Se sei l&amp;rsquo;owner hai anche la possibilità di:
 Inserire e modificare i dettagli di fatturazione;
 Effettuare l&amp;rsquo;import dei progetti utilizzando un apposito template.
  Team Since you are a Superuser you have the super power to: invite people, assign specific roles and allow special permissions.
Company Here you can configure your company by setting:
 User levels: each one of your collaborators has a level which defines his daily cost to the company and the price you want to sell a day of his work to the clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 17:08:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/faq/index/</guid>
      <description>(function(q,u,e,s,t,i,o,n) { o=u.getElementsByTagName(e)[0]; n=u.createElement(s),n.async=1,n.defer=1,n.src=i; o.appendChild(n) })(window,document,&#34;head&#34;,&#34;script&#34;,&#34;res_pars&#34;, &#34;https://goresponsa.com/widgets/57a0713be0e2ee8a8c001270.js&#34;);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 17:31:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/glossary/index/</guid>
      <description>Project Status Valore che indica la stima a finire per un certo progetto. In pratica esprime il numero di giorni mancanti alla fine del progetto.
Production Value Valore che indica &amp;ldquo;quanto un progetto ha prodotto&amp;rdquo; ovvero la percentuale di completamento * il valore del progetto. Ad esempio: un progetto con project status al di 40 su 100 giornate (gliene mancano 40 alla fine) e con valore 10K avrà production value = 10K * ((100 - 40)/100).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover WETHOD</title>
      <link>http://support.wethod.com/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://support.wethod.com/index/</guid>
      <description>What It Is WETHOD is the online tool to manage people and projects in a collaborative way. We aim to make the project management simple, distributing the responsibilities among all the team members and reducing stress derived from projects organization.
The result is a deeply integrated system that manages all the information which are essential for a project-oriented company: budget, planning, timesheet and activity report.
This enables WETHOD to create a system where everybody collaborate and keep information up to date, a system that rewards who done well and warns the others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>